http://www.3wheelerworld.com/privacy.html

What information do we collect? We collect
information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.
When ordering or
registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or
Geographical location. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.Google, as a third party
vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and
other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy
policy..What do we use your information for? Any of the information
we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: • To personalize your
experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)• To
improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information
and feedback we receive from you)• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other
site featureDo we use cookies? Yes (Cookies are small
files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser
(if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and
remember certain information We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future
visits and keep track of advertisements and .Do we disclose any information to outside
parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your
personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating
our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this
information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to
comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing,
advertising, or other uses.Third party links
Occasionally, at our
discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites
have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the
content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and
welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act
ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be
in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your
personal information to outside parties without your consent.As part of the California Online
Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by
logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.Childrens Online
Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA
(Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of
age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or
older.Terms and Conditions Please also visit our Terms and
Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our
website at http://www.3wheelerworld.com/tos.htmlYour Consent By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update
the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on 12-29-09Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you
may contact us using the information below. http://www.3wheelerworld.comP.O. Box 549Live oak, FL 32060USAadmins@3wheelerworld.comPrivacy Policy
